I love all the volunteer events.
I love all the fundraisers that we do.
I think that people should come and work for Utility Aid
because we really do care.
You get to speak to a lot of charities,
a lot of people who really need the help.
We all want to do things. It’s a big team.
We took part in Red August for a mental health charity.
We ran every day.
We actually covered 1500 miles between us.
When I handed over the big cheque,
they took me on a tour and it was amazing to see
there were so many people that had been saved
and it was really really special to see.
Utility Aid buys and sells energy for the charity sector.
It is an absolutely amazing space to operate in
because every single day we help charities save money.
Utility Aid is a great place to work
because we’re a caring company in a caring sector
and those who can bring that caring nature to us,
they are just going to excel.
We’ve also done a Steptober
which was doing as many steps as possible for the whole of October.
It didn’t matter if you were a strong walker,
a weak walker, it was a team effort.
We get two days paid leave a year to go and volunteer.
Everybody really really cares.
We did waitressing for 150 senior
citizens for their Christmas party.
We found out that a lot of them are really lonely.
They see everybody with people who are from their village.
When they go back home,
they have got somebody that they can talk to.
It was really really special.
One of the best parts of my job is getting to call customers up
and telling them that  they’ve saved a lot of money.
One time we called a women’s refuge
and told them they’d saved thousands and thousands of pounds.
They were over the moon.
I’ve never worked for anywhere so special.